<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>italics</title>
    <description>writepad for the soul
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:8082/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:8082/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 23:05:37 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 23:05:37 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Just Kidding</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;They said I’m just a kid with a noisy mind speaking out loud without thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Hopeless and irritating”, they cursed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some raised voices, some raised hands to beat some maturity into me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Few sympathized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Poor kid”, they pitied.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You see — I’m an adult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love being a kid. I loved playing video games in arcades, loved joking about silly stuff, loved sketching, loved licking cream from my hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess. I guess I loved a little too much.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I still do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What’s up dude? Why are you always being a jerk” — sometimes I daydream and frequently I imagine myself being angry at &lt;em&gt;Time.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a kid promise me that you’ll make a pinky promise with Time. Don’t let it run away from you. Hold hands. Love each other. Hug. Kiss.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sadly, there’s a problem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time isn’t a good friend. It’s bad company. It’s naughty, it’s crazy. It doesn’t get any presents from Santa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time doesn’t want you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Someday Time told me — I know I have let you down and I’m not going to apologize. I don’t owe you anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I cried, cried hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When my palms become warm by my tears dropping hard — I realized. I know it’s going to be alright.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I need to believe in me. I need to let go of time. Break the promise. You know what I learnt after so many fights with Time?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You are Time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just kidding, go fuck yourself. I have got work to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t you?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8082/2019/05/09/just-kidding/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8082/2019/05/09/just-kidding/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>DowryCoin Bride</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The end syllable “coin” had struck a considerable interest in the bridegrooms, fat and near bald father.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As he pursed his lips and rose his spectacle just up to look into his phone about Bitcoin…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…it hit him hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He was about to get rich, he dreamt, he drooled. He thought of all the scented toilet paper he could buy, the white gold for his missus and a majestic flat for the family….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…and soon found out the call he was in, had gone silent.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He wouldn’t allow this opportunity to pass like his playful habits of passing gas in crowds…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…fat thumbs which had committed sins because of greed, gluttony and lust, began furiously dialing the numbers of the Bitcoin bride…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…the reply he got was an eerie, static line at the other end, he dialed again and again and with passing time, a chill ran through his senile spine..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;..through the window he could see the near frozen haze of the evening as the sun went down…it was cold but he was sweating hard….&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;..finally the static gave away to his misery and he heard a woman’s voice..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…“hello?”, said the calm female voice, “I missed you so much!”… his eyes bulged, the very same mouth which acted like a sword, many times, had lost it’s voice..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;…a feeble gasp accompanied by horror escaped that vile mouth which made the tobacco soaked teeth clearly visible..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I missed you so much! papa!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right in the wall, up the corded phone, hung the picture of this daughter – his dead daughter decorated by flowers and respected by the pious paste of sandalwood.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2018 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8082/2018/05/25/DowryCoin-Bride/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8082/2018/05/25/DowryCoin-Bride/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Angel of a Demon</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;The best days of mine were spend in the arms of a beautiful women. &lt;br /&gt;
Mom, why do I cry when your arms are around me?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t cry, mother. I &lt;em&gt;laugh&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;
These tears are just cinders of love burning in the middle of the campfire which is my heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the best times to come and those which already have swayed away, I love thee from every dimension my heart echoes its beats.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The nights of sleep you sacrificed, the days of pain you endured, the best you have left for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am &lt;em&gt;nervous&lt;/em&gt;. I’m &lt;em&gt;scared.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first cry and laugh in your womb, the first touch of love, the first look in my eye, the first emotional bloom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reflection of evil, the carcass of love, the flower of the night, the force of the wild.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blood on the floor. The tears littered around. The dark seeping through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The maladies of life. The fear in me. The joke of the people. The strangeness around me. Oh mom, I’m scared of the venomous rife.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Days pass by.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;And age creeps into.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Soon it’s goodbye.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Never want that memory tattoo.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh mom, shine on me. Shine on me. Shine on me. &lt;br /&gt;
The music has gone slow and silent, I can hear my heart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My fingers tremble as I write and my soul shivers while I think. &lt;br /&gt;
Every emotion is a mirror of a malice. And every evil scattered has love inside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What a &lt;strong&gt;demon&lt;/strong&gt; am I for an &lt;strong&gt;angel&lt;/strong&gt; like you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love you.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8082/2017/05/18/Angel-of-a-demon/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8082/2017/05/18/Angel-of-a-demon/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>This Dusshera</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;October. 
Autumn freshness. 
Killer fireworks. 
Nostalgic sweets. 
Vibrant colours. 
Dusshera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This festival begs to be written for the memories, the color, the smiles of everyone is so beautiful. And something beautiful needs to be preserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rhythm of peoples hearts. There’s so much beauty in them. From babies to old people, hearts tell a lot of lovely stories. This Dusshera, let me tell mine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Against the dark backdrop of poverty and sadness that suck life like lice from the dirty social community tangled like filthy hair, India still has got hope.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That light inside kids who sleep hungry, that mother who bakes the rotis in swirling ashes for her kids in spite her lungs forming tears, that father who forgets the difference of sweat and blood to put food on the table, every single person who suffer for the evil are so tightly tied together in valiant threads, which weave out a proud fabric.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reality. The fabric of life, spiced with a pinch of cruelty. 
The end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Festivals don’t allow ends to be this grim, especially Dusshera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slum kids enjoy the songs, the fair as heartily as the rich bastards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sweets eaten by my postman are of same sweetness and rather more lovely and memorable than the sweets eaten by the rich bastards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bokeh of rainbow lights dancing in everyones irises that night doesn’t differentiate between rich and poor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;History says Dusshera is the festival where light defeats darkness. Good prevails the bad. Evil dies. Angels are born.
But in the end that’s not what Dusshera is about. It’s everyone being happy equally and smiling wide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Really wide.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8082/2016/10/03/this-dusshera/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8082/2016/10/03/this-dusshera/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Friends matter. A lot.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subterfuge.&lt;/strong&gt;
I was worried about it. That someone whom I know would warp my conscience and subterfuge with it. 
It ain’t now so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Believe.&lt;/strong&gt;
Bonding. Relations. The strong ones. The valiant sea that we sail. The mast that never breaks. The sails that fill their chests with pride. With you beside, I ain’t sinking anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Telepathy.&lt;/strong&gt;
A hocus in most eyes. A wonder in some. A dream. Connecting still being far. The humanely inhuman power to know about someone not with you. About the person you care. 
I thought it was a bluff as science wasn’t sure. 
I ain’t thinking that now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pain.&lt;/strong&gt;
A multidimensional entity. That can’t be shared. Which is harsh. From which you can’t run away. You are stuck. 
I was stoic. 
It ain’t so now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friendship.&lt;/strong&gt; 
A power from within the four chambered hearts. An emotion endless. A feeling of unity. The sunshine amidst the rain. 
I love it now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Subterfuge. Believe. Telepathy. Pain.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They all are different notations when you have true friendship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When words can only tell so much. When the feels take over. The heart races into a calm. The rough tides meet the tranquil. The transient yet eternal fractals of life shawn the orgasms of chaste spasms. It is the sentient presence of the friend spirit that pacifies the Pacific. A true silence is born, potent with eternity itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure I know of this silence.
I am sure I have one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for curing me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you being here.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8082/2016/08/07/friendship/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8082/2016/08/07/friendship/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It's Father's Day!</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;cheese-grapes-and-a-jug-of-wine&quot;&gt;Cheese, grapes and a jug of wine.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1966, President Lyndon B. Johnson issued the first presidential proclamation honoring fathers, designating the third Sunday in June as Father’s Day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That third Sunday this year is today. June 19 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Roses.&lt;/em&gt; I woke up and saw roses. Roses in my garden. White and red.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Birds.&lt;/em&gt; I saw birds flying in the sky. Free. Honoring their liberation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mongoose.&lt;/em&gt; I saw a chain of mongeese swiftly crossing the road, the little ones, tail to tail. Love and care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ants.&lt;/em&gt; I saw them working hard for their hill. For life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cats.&lt;/em&gt; I saw a cat, majestic and calmly licking it’s paw.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, I saw my &lt;em&gt;father&lt;/em&gt;. Drinking coffee. &lt;br /&gt;
Déjà vu hit me. 
My father was all of the thoughts that clouded my mind this morning while I was at the garden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our relation is different. Silent and powerful. Calm and free. Caring and discipline. We don’t hang out a lot. 
Our taste in movies is different.
Our taste in songs is different. 
Our taste in some routine life is different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My father is pure and powerful in his heart as the roses. He sees me as his bird as I’m let free to do anything. He is caring and loving in his own way which is different but as I told you, in a good way. He works hard like an ant, and though doesn’t spend much time with me, he is always present when I need him. He pivots my life when it goes astray. He is calm and very understanding and respects many ideas that I give around the dinner table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This journey of father and son is an unique one. It’s the slash of red grapes and the juice of emotions. It’s tenderly strong. He is the bright sunlight that shines in my gloomy mind. He silent, but strong. He is watching me, every step that I tread my weary path. The flowers bloom in my road are watered by him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is my dark knight. &lt;br /&gt;
He is Batman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Happy Fathers Day Dad!.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love him for being what he was, what he is and what he will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh boy, I would like to take him surfing some day, or maybe sit and talk with some cheese, grapes and a jug of wine?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8082/2016/06/19/It's-Father's-Day/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8082/2016/06/19/It's-Father's-Day/</guid>
        
        <category>life</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mothers Love.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;12:15 am&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s midnight. &lt;br /&gt;
I am on Quora. As usual. &lt;br /&gt;
My mother comes to my room, and sits beside me. &lt;br /&gt;
This conversation starts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mom&lt;/strong&gt; : When will go to sleep? &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Me&lt;/strong&gt; : Just after a minute. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Mom&lt;/strong&gt; : Really? &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Me&lt;/strong&gt; : Yes, don’t worry, you go to sleep, I will sleep now. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Mom&lt;/strong&gt; : Then,  go and brush now. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Me&lt;/strong&gt; : Yes, I  will. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Mom&lt;/strong&gt; : Let me sit here till you come back from brushing. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Me&lt;/strong&gt; : I will go, please go and sleep. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Mom&lt;/strong&gt; : No, I will wait till I see you asleep. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Me&lt;/strong&gt; : Mom, I just figured I have to watch the new episode of Arrow.
I will be sleeping late, Mom. Around 1 am, so go and sleep. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Mom&lt;/strong&gt; : When will you take care of yourself? Okay. Sleep before 1am. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Me&lt;/strong&gt; : Yes, Mom definitely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She goes to her room. All lights are off of the house except mine. After brushing, I start watching Arrow. ( &lt;em&gt;only one episode as promised to my Mother.&lt;/em&gt;) &lt;br /&gt;
It’s almost 1 am.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1:45 am&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finish watching an episode of Arrow. As the suspense is unbearable,  I watch another episode of Arrow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2:30 am&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finish watching another episode. (&lt;em&gt;Sorry for the lie, mom&lt;/em&gt;) &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;It’s 2:30 am.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
My mother walks in, again. &lt;br /&gt;
Conversation follows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mom&lt;/strong&gt; : What time is it now! &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Me&lt;/strong&gt; : Err,… Umm. I don’t know. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Mom&lt;/strong&gt; : 2:30 am! You told me you will sleep before 1 am!!!. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Me&lt;/strong&gt; : I’m hungry, mom. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Mom&lt;/strong&gt;: I had told you to take one more roti. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Me&lt;/strong&gt;(&lt;em&gt;thinking&lt;/em&gt;) : I get it now &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Mom&lt;/strong&gt; : Wait, let me go and  heat milk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goes to &lt;strong&gt;heat milk at 2:30 am for me, after a tiring and hard day.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
Comes back with warm milk and some biscuits. :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I greedily eat while she pats me and advises me to sleep early and eat properly. &lt;br /&gt;
I goof and joke around. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;She&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;em&gt;laughs.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
I do, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;She says&lt;/strong&gt; : “Always keep laughing irrespective you study, or do anything. I will be happy.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Me&lt;/strong&gt; (&lt;em&gt;internally tears forming, and loving her more.&lt;/em&gt;) : Yes Mom, you too keep laughing, always.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s &lt;strong&gt;3 am&lt;/strong&gt; in the morning. &lt;br /&gt;
I go to sleep and she goes too. &lt;br /&gt;
All lights are off. &lt;br /&gt;
It’s dark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3:15 am&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am still awake, on my bed. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Insomnia, perhaps.&lt;/em&gt; I try to make those eyelids fall, but all effort goes in vain. &lt;br /&gt;
I start reading Quora. ;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3:45 am&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suddenly, I hear her footsteps, for her feet wears those &lt;em&gt;pretty leg-ankle jewelry-chain&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;br /&gt;
( I don’t know what the word is, and I’m too lazy now to search it up).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I suddenly close my phone, face the screen down and play to be asleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mother enters my room. She checks if I’m sleeping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Covers my cold feet with the blanket. &lt;br /&gt;
Caresses my hair, kisses me on the forehead, and says good night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s 4 am.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will probably wake up late, at &lt;strong&gt;11 am&lt;/strong&gt;, but she &lt;strong&gt;has to wake up at 7 am&lt;/strong&gt; for her work calls, which will, again be for me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;She &lt;em&gt;slept only&lt;/em&gt; after she checked if I slept. &lt;br /&gt;
She &lt;strong&gt;stayed almost the whole night awake&lt;/strong&gt;, just for me. &lt;br /&gt;
Indian Moms are so awesome and amazing, isn’t?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;She loves me dearly. And…&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;em&gt;And, such is mother’s love.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4:15 am&lt;/strong&gt; :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I, totally amazed by a mother’s love, keep thinking about hope and love that makes the world such a beautiful place. It doesn’t matter where the hell we are, how old we are and how bad our situation is. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Mother’s love is always, always there for you.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;You are still in the womb of her love.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Sacrifice is immense, and so is her tender, gentle and genuine love.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I love you, mom.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4:20 am&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I start writing this on Quora. &lt;br /&gt;
;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This answer was posted on Quora on 29th October, 2015 at around 4:40 am. It had got 29.6k upvotes and 200+ comments. Sadly, as good things stay short the question was deleted, deleting this answer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The answer might be deleted, but my memories and love for her will never.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ankit &lt;br /&gt;
Her proud &lt;strong&gt;son&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:8082/2015/10/29/mother's-love/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8082/2015/10/29/mother's-love/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
