<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>italics</title>
    <description>writepad for the soul
</description>
    <link>https://sudoankit.github.iohttps://sudoankit.github.io/italics//</link>
    <atom:link href="https://sudoankit.github.iohttps://sudoankit.github.io/italics//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 10:42:29 +0530</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2016 10:42:29 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>This Dusshera</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;October. 
Autumn freshness. 
Killer fireworks. 
Nostalgic sweets. 
Vibrant colours. 
Dusshera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This festival begs to be written for the memories, the color, the smiles of everyone is so beautiful. And something beautiful needs to be preserved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rhythm of peoples hearts. There’s so much beauty in them. From babies to old people, hearts tell a lot of lovely stories. This Dusshera, let me tell mine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Against the dark backdrop of poverty and sadness that suck life like lice from the dirty social community tangled like filthy hair, India still has got hope.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That light inside kids who sleep hungry, that mother who bakes the rotis in swirling ashes for her kids in spite her lungs forming tears, that father who forgets the difference of sweat and blood to put food on the table, every single person who suffer for the evil are so tightly tied together in valiant threads, which weave out a proud fabric.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reality. The fabric of life, spiced with a pinch of cruelty. 
The end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Festivals don’t allow ends to be this grim, especially Dusshera.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slum kids enjoy the songs, the fair as heartily as the rich bastards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sweets eaten by my postman are of same sweetness and rather more lovely and memorable than the sweets eaten by the rich bastards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bokeh of rainbow lights dancing in everyones irises that night doesn’t differentiate between rich and poor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;History says Dusshera is the festival where light defeats darkness. Good prevails the bad. Evil dies. Angels are born.
But in the end that’s not what Dusshera is about. It’s everyone being happy equally and smiling wide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Really wide.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://sudoankit.github.iohttps://sudoankit.github.io/italics//2016/10/03/this-dusshera/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sudoankit.github.iohttps://sudoankit.github.io/italics//2016/10/03/this-dusshera/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Pink Cherry Blossoms</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I remember what I had seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;White drapes, white sarees, white sky.&lt;/em&gt; I saw white everywhere. I had come to meet my sister after a long long time. Little did I know, that those whites weren’t the peaceful ones, those whites were something that I feared all my life and continue to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know what’s white also?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;…the white packet of cigarettes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world had stopped for something she wasn’t ready for. She hadn’t done anything wrong. She just wanted to ease the pain. More and more she tried to ease, not knowing she was praying indirectly to ease herself too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When they looked into her eyes, they were scared but still &lt;em&gt;warm&lt;/em&gt;. Warm, comforting and helpful were her qualities which she left printed on her comrades.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the smile that &lt;em&gt;won hearts&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;the personality that made men cry out&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;the charming glee of her sisterhood&lt;/em&gt;, she had abandon all sang sadly to the monotonous tone of a &lt;em&gt;cigarette&lt;/em&gt; whistle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s said that death is peaceful and how correct it was! She couldn’t take a puff and ease the pain nor I could &lt;em&gt;see the amber dull glow of the cigarette end dance in her iris.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pink cherry blossoms&lt;/em&gt; fell on her, at 5 centimetres per second. People who loved cried around her, talked is hushed tones, and uttered sermons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The clouds hurried to cry too, and before I realised what had happened, rain wet me but lost to &lt;em&gt;my tears wetting my heart from inside&lt;/em&gt; for lay in front of me, was my sister is white. Everything else was grey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I stood and knelt beside her, thinking the colourful days. I gave her some flowers to smell which her body graced after the torture by the cigarettes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The rain, the atmosphere, the people, the soil, the soul, the life, her, me everything were stitched to make me think that this wouldn’t be true if she had listened to me…&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;…..as a drop of water left her finger and fell down to water, a flower beneath, I left how I had come, but without a sister.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;and life wasn’t same again&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life won’t be the same again&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, believe me I know that feeling very well. When she died, life never become the same again&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good Night. Sweet dreams. Don’t cry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Don’t cry because of cigarettes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The life you are living now won’t be with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The food you order, the smiles you share with friends, the talk we do, the hawa wala place, the crushes you get on teachers, the emotions, the cry, the tears. Every single thing you love will be taken away by &lt;em&gt;just a cigarette.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;:) Ankit.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://sudoankit.github.iohttps://sudoankit.github.io/italics//2016/08/07/pink-cherry-blossom/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sudoankit.github.iohttps://sudoankit.github.io/italics//2016/08/07/pink-cherry-blossom/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Friends matter. A lot.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Subterfuge.&lt;/strong&gt;
I was worried about it. That someone whom I know would warp my conscience and subterfuge with it. 
It ain’t now so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Believe.&lt;/strong&gt;
Bonding. Relations. The strong ones. The valiant sea that we sail. The mast that never breaks. The sails that fill their chests with pride. With you beside, I ain’t sinking anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Telepathy.&lt;/strong&gt;
A hocus in most eyes. A wonder in some. A dream. Connecting still being far. The humanely inhuman power to know about someone not with you. About the person you care. 
I thought it was a bluff as science wasn’t sure. 
I ain’t thinking that now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pain.&lt;/strong&gt;
A multidimensional entity. That can’t be shared. Which is harsh. From which you can’t run away. You are stuck. 
I was stoic. 
It ain’t so now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Friendship.&lt;/strong&gt; 
A power from within the four chambered hearts. An emotion endless. A feeling of unity. The sunshine amidst the rain. 
I love it now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Family.&lt;/strong&gt; 
Sharing is caring. Caring is family. Family is being a sister. Being a sister with you makes the world more beautiful. 
I’m so thankful for being with me as a sister.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Subterfuge. Believe. Telepathy. Pain. Family.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They all are different notations when you have true friendship.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When words can only tell so much. When the feels take over. The heart races into a calm. The rough tides meet the tranquil. The transient yet eternal fractals of life shawn the orgasms of chaste spasms. It is the sentient presence of the friend spirit that pacifies the Pacific. A true silence is born, potent with eternity itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am sure I know of this silence.
I am sure I have one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for curing me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you being here.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://sudoankit.github.iohttps://sudoankit.github.io/italics//2016/08/07/friendship/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sudoankit.github.iohttps://sudoankit.github.io/italics//2016/08/07/friendship/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>It's Father's Day!</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;cheese-grapes-and-a-jug-of-wine&quot;&gt;Cheese, grapes and a jug of wine.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 1966, President Lyndon B. Johnson issued the first presidential proclamation honoring fathers, designating the third Sunday in June as Father’s Day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That third Sunday this year is today. June 19 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Roses.&lt;/em&gt; I woke up and saw roses. Roses in my garden. White and red.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Birds.&lt;/em&gt; I saw birds flying in the sky. Free. Honoring their liberation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Mongoose.&lt;/em&gt; I saw a chain of mongeese swiftly crossing the road, the little ones, tail to tail. Love and care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ants.&lt;/em&gt; I saw them working hard for their hill. For life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cats.&lt;/em&gt; I saw a cat, majestic and calmly licking it’s paw.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, I saw my &lt;em&gt;father&lt;/em&gt;. Drinking coffee. &lt;br /&gt;
Déjà vu hit me. 
My father was all of the thoughts that clouded my mind this morning while I was at the garden.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our relation is different. Silent and powerful. Calm and free. Caring and discipline. We don’t hang out a lot. 
Our taste in movies is different.
Our taste in songs is different. 
Our taste in some routine life is different.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My father is pure and powerful in his heart as the roses. He sees me as his bird as I’m let free to do anything. He is caring and loving in his own way which is different but as I told you, in a good way. He works hard like an ant, and though doesn’t spend much time with me, he is always present when I need him. He pivots my life when it goes astray. He is calm and very understanding and respects many ideas that I give around the dinner table.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This journey of father and son is an unique one. It’s the slash of red grapes and the juice of emotions. It’s tenderly strong. He is the bright sunlight that shines in my gloomy mind. He silent, but strong. He is watching me, every step that I tread my weary path. The flowers bloom in my road are watered by him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He is my dark knight. &lt;br /&gt;
He is Batman.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Happy Fathers Day Dad!.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love him for being what he was, what he is and what he will be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh boy, I would like to take him surfing some day, or maybe sit and talk with some cheese, grapes and a jug of wine?&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>https://sudoankit.github.iohttps://sudoankit.github.io/italics//2016/06/19/It's-Father's-Day/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sudoankit.github.iohttps://sudoankit.github.io/italics//2016/06/19/It's-Father's-Day/</guid>
        
        <category>life</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
